do you have
advice for people
uh that want to you know get into
programming want to learn programming
you have a
video uh what is programming new
blessings exclamation point and i think
the top comment is like warning this is
not for noobs
uh do you have a noob
like uh tldw for that video but also
uh a new but friendly
advice on how to get into programming
you are never going to learn programming
by watching a video
called learn programming the only way to
learn programming i think and the only
one is
the only way everyone i've ever met who
can program well they learned it all in
the same way
they had something they wanted to do
and then they tried to do it and then
they were like
oh well okay this is kind of you know be
nice if the computer could kind of do
this thing and then
you know that's how you learn you just
keep pushing on a project
um so the only advice i have for
learning programming is go program
somebody wrote to me a question like we
don't really
they're looking to learn about recurrent
neural networks
and saying like my company's thinking of
doing using recurring neural networks
for time series data
but we don't really have an idea of
where to use it yet
we just want to like do you have any
advice on how to learn about
these are these kind of general machine
learning questions and i think
the answer is like actually
have a problem that you're trying to
solve and and just i see that stuff oh
my god when people talk like that
they're like
i heard machine learning's important
could you help us integrate machine
learning with macaroni and cheese
production
you just i don't even you can't help
these people like who lets you
run anything who lets that kind of
person run anything
i think we're we're all um we're all
beginners at some point so
it's not like they're a beginner it's
it's like my problem is not that they
don't know about machine learning
my problem is that they think that
machine learning has something to say
about macaroni and cheese production
or like i heard about this new
technology how can i use it for why
like i don't know what it is but how can
i use it for why
that's true you have to build a
penetration of how because you might be
able to figure out a way but
like the prerequisites you should have a
macaroni and cheese problem to solve
first exactly
and then two you should have more
traditional like
in the learning process should involve
more traditionally applicable problems
in the space of whatever that is of
machine learning and then see if it
could be
applied to background at least start
with tell me about a problem like if you
have a problem you're like
you know some of my boxes aren't getting
enough macaroni in them
um can we use machine learning to solve
this problem that's
much much better than how do i apply
machine learning to macaroni and cheese
you