<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Upwork on Imlauer</title>
    <link>https://imlauera.github.io/tags/upwork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Upwork on Imlauer</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>es-es</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 22:43:03 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://imlauera.github.io/tags/upwork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Upwork invited</title>
      <link>https://imlauera.github.io/post/upwork_invited/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 22:43:03 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imlauera.github.io/post/upwork_invited/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Outlier helps the world’s most innovative companies improve their AI models by providing human feedback. Are you an experienced software engineer who would like to lend your coding expertise to train AI models in Chilean Spanish?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We partner with organizations to train AI large language models, helping cutting-edge generative AI models write better code. Projects typically include discrete, highly variable problems that involve engaging with these models as they learn to code. There is no requirement for previous AI experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upwork scams</title>
      <link>https://imlauera.github.io/post/upwork_scams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 19:41:58 -0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://imlauera.github.io/post/upwork_scams/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Para evitar la mayoría de estafas en UpWork es recomendable usar los siguientes filtros.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Paso 1:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Información de clientes: Payment verified (pago verificado)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Client history (historial de clientes): 1 to 9 hires or 10+ hires (De 1 a 9 contratados o más de 10 contratados)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Fijate las reseñas de los freelancers que trabajaron con ese cliente.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Paso 2:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alguna de las cosas que indican una mala señal son clientes que tardan en contestar o que nunca están felices con el trabajo que hacen los demás freelancers. O los clientes que siempre te piden hacer más trabajo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
